lotterypost.com 2004-12-07

# Lottery Post: Lottery Post Privacy Statement

**Welcome  Guest**  
( [Log In](https://www.lotterypost.com/login.asp "Log in to your Lottery Post account") | [Register](http://www.lotterypost.com/register_form.asp "Become a Lottery Post member") )  
  
|  Lottery Post Links   
---  
  
· [Home](http://www.lotterypost.com/ "Lottery Post Home Page")

· [Discussion Forums](http://www.lotterypost.com/forums.htm "Go to the Lottery Post forums")

· [Lottery Predictions](http://www.lotterypost.com/predictions.htm "View and post lottery predictions")

· [Lottery News](http://www.lotterypost.com/news.htm "See the latest lottery news presented by month")

· [Lottery Results](http://www.lotterypost.com/lottery-results.htm "See the latest lottery results")

· [Search Past Results](http://www.lotterypost.com/lottery-results-search.asp "Search past lottery drawing results for any game")

· [Lottery Jackpots](http://www.lotterypost.com/jackpots.htm "See the current US, Canada, and UK lottery jackpots")

· [Member Blogs](http://www.lotterypost.com/blogs.asp "Lottery Post member journals \(Blogs\)")

· [Quick Picks Generator](http://www.lotterypost.com/quickpicks.asp "Have the Lottery Post computer generate random lottery ticket numbers for you")

· [Contact Us](http://www.lotterypost.com/contact.asp "Send e-mail to Lottery Post")

· [Rules](http://www.lotterypost.com/rules.asp "The rules to make sure our forum is a friendly helpful place for lottery information")

· [Privacy Statement](http://www.lotterypost.com/privacy.asp "We respect your privacy!")

* * *

 **Click  a Game to Play**

 **$171 Million**

 **$30 Million**

 **$23 Million**

 **$15 Million**

 **$10 Million**

 **$6 Million**

 **$2.42 Billion**

* * *

---  
  
---  
Nancy Moser  
New $8.07!  
Used $2.99! |   
Steve Ledoux |   
Gail Howard |   
RON ROY |   
Isaac E. Nwokogba |   
Iliya Bluskov |   
Gail Howard |   
(Prices May Change)  

NetConnect

Internet domains, simple and cheap

Find a domain name:  
  
---  

The time is now 3:50 pm

 Home -> Lottery Post Privacy Statement  

|  Lottery Post Privacy Statement   
---  
  
The Lottery Post privacy policy is simple:   

  * When browsing Lottery Post forums and messages, no personally identifying information is collected or used.
  * When you register as a Lottery Post Member, we will collect minimal personal information, including e-mail address and country. Much of what we ask for is optional.
  * We do not provide any third party company or individual with any of the information that is posted on Lottery Post, or that is provided when you register.
  * When you post a message or when you register to become a member, we put a "cookie" on your PC for your convenience. The cookie's main function is to retain your login information on your PC so you don't have to retype it the next time you post a message. The cookie takes up practically no space on your PC hard drive, and is completely harmless.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us.  
  
This page was generated in 0.0156 seconds  
Copyright © 1999-2004 Big Game LLC.  All rights reserved.
